<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HuveeWong Blog</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on HuveeWong Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:00:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Semester 4 Update</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-4-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:00:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-4-update/</guid><description>&lt;p>
Is been awhile since I last update anything here, It was an eventful semester. Learned quite a lot on how to be a developer and spent an unholy amount of time infront of my monitor. On the previous post, I said that I will remake this page into something more interesting. I'm afraid I'll have to postpone that idea and work on other aspect in my life. On a side note, I think I'm biting off more than I can chew right now with all the upcoming events in April while trying to learn plenty of different stuff. Such as: React, Laravel, Ruby on Rails, and Java.
&lt;p>Hopefully I return with some good news in 4 months!
So long.&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Semester 3</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:10:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>
Greeting Again,
&lt;p>It was a quick 4 months a lot happened. Working hard and also gaming hard this semester. Spending countless hours on Project Zomboid and currently Modded Minecraft. Even capable of finishing a TV series during my 2 weeks break. Proudest achievement this semester has to be finishing Nier:Replicant ending A/B/C/D. I will do my best to finish the E ending as well because I&amp;rsquo;m really not good at playing singleplayer video game if you know me well.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>1 important lesson I learned this semester is that rely on AI more. It was not worth the trouble to work until late night to come up with a clean code because not a single soul will value your work. If you are interest to check out what hot mess I wrote is right &lt;a href="https://github.com/huveewomg/PWP-Assignment">here&lt;/a>. Frankly speaking, I can&amp;rsquo;t recall most of the stuff happened this semester.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>See you in 4 months. Hopefully I done something by then.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Update (28/10): Do expect for a remake for this entire website. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking to integrate some API like LastFM on here if I have the time.&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Semester 2</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:10:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>
Before I knew it, today is the last week before my third semester starts. Semester 2 was by far the worst one I have had in a while. Working with more than 14 passive people in a group over the course of 12 weeks has taken quite a toll on me. Other than that, everything else went smoothly, and I visited more places than I did last year. I had planned to visit the infamous cult, but unfortunately, the cult members are too lazy to even raise funds to revive their leaders. At the same time, I managed to meet more people from around the world. Hopefully, semester 3 will treat me nicely.
&lt;p>See you in another 4 months~&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Semester 1</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:42:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/semester-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>
Is been awhile since the last time I write a post here and I'm quite free at the moment so I decided to write something. 3-4 months ago I enrolled for a university studying Software Engineering but to my suprise I spent the entire first semester studying nothing related to it. Ended up spending my time on game and automating task.
&lt;p>I wish you a early Merry Christmas and Happy new year !
早めのメリクリ、あけおめ！来年もよろしくお願いします。&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Struggle</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/struggle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 20:43:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/struggle/</guid><description>&lt;p>
If you're reading this article there is a good chance I successfully deploy this site on github pages without using alternative method such as netlify or anything similar.
&lt;p>Update : After 5 days of procastination I finally manage to deploy this site. 30/5&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why I Made This Site</title><link>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/why-i-made-this-site/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:08:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://huveewomg.github.io/blog/why-i-made-this-site/</guid><description>&lt;h1> Here Is Why &lt;/h1>
&lt;p>
During the journey of learning language I met a nice person who is a web devs and he inspired me to try out something new.
&lt;p>Making a website has always been one of them. I spent hours a year ago to learn the basic of markup languages yet didnt make anything with it. I procastinated a lot even though I have all the time in the word at the moment. Yesterday, I challenged myself to sit down and spend a day and do it and this is the end result.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Frankly speaking I&amp;rsquo;m quite proud of how things turns out.
Despite the fact I forgot most of the syntax but is painless to get back to them. Thank you my friend !&lt;/p>
&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>